classifieds2india.com 2015-06-07

# 

classifieds2india.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. The following Privacy Policy acts as a guide you to understand how your personal information will be treated when you make use of our Website. This policy may be change or Updated from time to time with out any Prior Notice.

**Collection of Personal Information:**  
When you register on classifieds2india.com.com, then your personal information such as your name, Email id, Mobile Number, Address, Phone number etc are required at registration time. On registration you will receive an Email of your E-mail id and password. In addition we may ask you for personal information at other times when you place ads or use other features of the classifieds2india.com

Contact information provided may be used to contact customers when necessary. We collect customers financial information (such as account Number and Details or credit card numbers) to bill the user for products and services, but retain this information only as required to process the transaction and for as long as may be required by law.

We use contact data from our surveys to send users information about our products and services. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings. We may use user information for additional purposes that may be identified at or before the time that the information is collected. We also use information from customers for accounting and transaction completion purposes.

We use third-party advertising companies like Google to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information, specifically for Google, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**With whom do we share your information?**  
classifieds2india.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services. 

classifieds2india.com will not disclose your personal information unless we have your permission or under special circumstances. classifieds2india.com may disclose account information only when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Service of the Site or if it is causing injury to or interference in rights or property, other users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

We may disclose certain personal information as follows:   
\- by publishing ads either online and or in print, as the case may be, in connection with items that are for sale by customers   
\- to law enforcement agencies for the purposes of investigating fraud or other offences, or   
\- to legal, financial, and other professional advisors or in connection with the sale or reorganization of all or part of its business or operations.   
Except as provided above, we will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required or permitted by law. 

**Use Cookies and IP Addresses:**  
We may use your IP address to identify you and your membership, Personal information about our users, diagnose problems with our server, and administrator of the Site. The Site uses cookies to track of your membership tools and to make sure you do not see the same Classified ads repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site. We also provide an option to log out should you be using an insecure or publicly shared computer. We use outside ad companies to display ads on the Site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of the Site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information.

**Links:**  
This Site contains links to other websites, such as websites providing national search capabilities and information resources designed to inform buyers and sellers about general aspects of property that is being sold. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Please ensure you review the privacy policies of the websites that you visit. 

**Security Precautions Services:**   
We protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information with security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, it is possible that any information transmitted via the Internet may be intercepted by unknown third parties. We use our network servers in a secure encrypted mode. 

**Corrections/or Contact:**  
Users of this Site may contact Classifieds2india to modify or correct any of their personal information that is under our control. (i) opt-out of receiving communications from us; (ii) remove their information from our database. An individual may also direct a written complaint regarding compliance with this Privacy Statement to us and, within a reasonable time upon receiving the written complaint, we will conduct an investigation into the matter, and we will take necessary measure/s to rectify the source of the complaint, as appropriate. 

**For Further Assistance Please Contact Us**   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement and practices in connection with this Site, or our collection, use, disclosure, or retention of your personal information in connection with this Site, please write us at feedback [at] classifieds2india.com.
